Andreas Munk

PhD Student, Computer Science



https://ammunk.com



Social Network -



in/andreas-munk



About Me

I am pursuing a PhD in Computer Science at the University of British Columbia, supervised by Frank Wood. My research areas are probabilistic programming, machine learning, and their application in real-world problems. I am specifically interested in Bayesian inference and (conditional) generative modeling using deep learning and how these two frameworks may be combined by leveraging probabilistic programming.

Programming

0 LOC >10,000 LOC

Python

Julia • Clojure • Matlab

C • C++ • R • Mathematica



<u>₽</u>T_EX

Languages

Danish



German



Education

2018 – 2022 (expected)	PhD. Computer Science Focus: Machine learning and a	University of British Columbia, Canada rtificial intelligence
2016 – 2018	MSc. Technical University of Denmark, Denmark Mathematical Modelling and Computation (GPA: 11.8/12.0)	
2015 – 2015	Exchange student (GPA: 3.6/4.0)	California Institute of Technology, USA
2013 – 2016	BSc. Earth and Space Physics and E	Technical University of Denmark, Denmark ngineering (GPA: 10.9/12.0)

Working Experience

Academic Experience and Teachings

2017	leaching Assistant	Technical University of Denmark, Denmark
	Course: Introduction to Machine	e Learning and Data Mining
2016	Teaching Assistant	Technical University of Denmark, Denmark
	Course: Continuous and Discrete Time Signals	
2014 – 2015	Teaching Assistant	Technical University of Denmark, Denmark
	Course: Advanced engineering mathematics 1	

Industrial Experience

2017 Internship Canecto, Copenhagen
In charge of building the company's core machine learning models

Scholarships and Awards

2018 – 2022	Faculty of Science PhD Tu	ition Award University of British Columbia
	Amount: 5460 CAD/yr	
2018 – 2022	International Tuition Awa	rd University of British Columbia
	Amount: 3200 CAD/yr	
2018	Research travel grant	IEEE Signal Processing Society (SPS)
	Amount: 3700 DKK	
2018	Research travel grant	DTU Compute, Denmark
2040	Amount: 7600 DKK	
2018	Research travel grant	Otto Mønsteds Fond, Denmark
2016	Amount: 6700 DKK	Company C. W. Coniglian askalanakia Basanania
2016	Academic funding	Garvermester C. W. Gerickes scholarship, Denmark
2015	Amount: 6000 DKK Academic funding	Technical University of Denmark Denmark
2013	_	reclinical diliversity of Definiark, Definiark
2015		Frk. Marie Månssons scholarship. Denmark
	-	, , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , ,
2015	Academic funding	Otto Mønsteds Fond, Denmark
	Amount: 10000 DKK	
2015	Amount: 6000 DKK Academic funding Amount: 10000 DKK Academic funding	Technical University of Denmark, Denmark Frk. Marie Månssons scholarship, Denmark Otto Mønsteds Fond, Denmark

Other programming frameworks

Probabilistic Programming Languages

PyProb – Contributor Anglican • Pyro

Machine Learning and Scientific Computing Libraries

PyTorch • TensorFlow • Scikit-Learn • Numpy • SciPy

Andreas Munk

PhD Student, Computer Science



ttps://ammunk.com



Social Network



in/andreas-munk

ammunk

About Me

I am pursuing a PhD in Computer Science at the University of British Columbia, supervised by Frank Wood. My research areas are probabilistic programming, machine learning, and their application in real-world problems. I am specifically interested in Bayesian inference and (conditional) generative modeling using deep learning and how these two frameworks may be combined by leveraging probabilistic programming.

Programming

0 LOC >10,000 LOC

Python

Julia • Clojure • Matlab

C • C++ • R • Mathematica

F HTML 5

ΔΤΕΧ

Languages

Danish

English

German



Publications

- [1] Atilim Güneş Baydin, Lei Shao, Wahid Bhimji, Lukas Heinrich, Lawrence Meadows, Jialin Liu, Andreas Munk, Saeid Naderiparizi, Bradley Gram-Hansen, Gilles Louppe, et al. "Etalumis: bringing probabilistic programming to scientific simulators at scale". In: *Proceedings of the International Conference for High Performance Computing, Networking, Storage and Analysis*. ACM. 2019, p. 29.
- [2] Atilim Gunes Baydin, Lei Shao, Wahid Bhimji, Lukas Heinrich, Saeid Naderi-parizi, Andreas Munk, Jialin Liu, Bradley Gram-Hansen, Gilles Louppe, Lawrence Meadows, et al. "Efficient probabilistic inference in the quest for physics beyond the standard model". In: Advances in Neural Information Processing Systems. 2019, pp. 5460–5473.
- [3] William Harvey, Andreas Munk, Atılım Güneş Baydin, Alexander Bergholm, and Frank Wood. "Attention for Inference Compilation". In: arXiv preprint arXiv:1910.1 (2019).
- [4] Andreas Munk, Adam Ścibior, Atılım Güneş Baydin, Andrew Stewart, Goran Fernlund, Anoush Poursartip, and Frank Wood. "Deep Probabilistic Surrogate Networks for Universal Simulator Approximation". In: arXiv preprint arXiv:1910.11 (2019).
- [5] Saeid Naderiparizi, Adam Ścibior, Andreas Munk, Mehrdad Ghadiri, Atılım Güneş Baydin, Bradley Gram-Hansen, Christian Schroeder de Witt, Robert Zinkov, Philip HS Torr, Tom Rainforth, et al. "Amortized Rejection Sampling in Universal Probabilistic Programming". In: arXiv preprint arXiv:1910.09056 (2019).
- [6] A. M. Munk, K. V. Olesen, S. W. Gangstad, and L. K. Hansen. "Semi-Supervised Sleep-Stage Scoring Based on Single Channel EEG". In: 2018 IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP). 2018, pp. 2551–2555. DOI: 10.1109/ICASSP.2018.8461982.